Policewoman: Good evening, Madam.
Are you Hannah Davis?
Hannah: Yes.
Yes, I am.
Policewoman: I’d like to speak to you.
Can I come in?
Are you a friend of Jamie Dixon?
Hannah: Er, yes.
Policewoman: Well, I’m afraid I have some bad news for you.
Hannah: What? What’s happened?
Policewoman: Jamie had an accident this evening.
Hannah: Oh no.
What kind of accident?
Policewoman: He was crossing the road and a car hit him.
Hannah: When…when did this happen? And where?
Policewoman: This evening at twenty-five past five.
He was crossing the road, near the theatre.
Hannah: Oh no! How is he?
Policewoman: He’s in hospital.
He’s got a bad injury to his head and two broken legs.
Hannah: But is he going to be OK?
Policewoman: We don’t know.
He’s in intensive care.
Hannah: Oh no.
And the driver of the car?
Policewoman: She didn’t stop.
Hannah: She?
Policewoman: Yes, it was a woman in a black car.
Somebody saw the number of the car.
You have a black car outside, don’t you, Madam?
Is your number plate G-Y five six, R-Z-R?
Hannah: Yes…yes, it is.
Policewoman: Can you tell me where you were at twenty-five past five this evening?